NOAM ACKERMAN

Frontend developer.

Email: developer.noam@gmail.com

Phone: +972505954084

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/noam-ackerman/

Summary

I am Noam Ackerman, based back in Israel after living in Berlin for 5 Years.

I've started my coding journey studying at "SheCodes USA" and in my previous job I worked as a Frontend developer at "Nosto Solutions" (using React, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, etc...).

I'm also a musician (singer, songwriter, instrumentalist and music producer) and a visual artist.

I am curious, passionate and diligent, with a strong will power. I enjoy challenges and solving problems.

I value a healthy, productive and respectful communication.

Skills

- Proficient with various technologies & languages such as React.js, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Git, API, jQuery, Responsive development
- Proficient with various software tools such as VS codes, Figma, Slack, Jira, Photoshop, Illustrator, Ableton
- Team player, fast learner, problem solver and highly creative

Experience

2021 - 2023 - Frontend Developer at "Nosto Solutions" an Ecommerce Experience Platform

- · Creating dynamic, interactive and responsive interfaces used by thousands of costumers daily
- · Fullfiling hundreds of Jira tickets and taking ownership of features from figma to production
- Investigating different site environments of merchants, creating solutions and fixing bugs
- · Developing mockups and wireframes for UI and optimized UX
- Initiating and leading a new team workflow guidelines and creating documents to increase team
 productivity and optimize project management efficiency
- · Providing technical guidance to merchants

2021 - 2023 - Updating my portfolio with projects I've built using several languages and technologies Public at – www.noamackerman.com

Highlighted projects:

- Post Your Thought A social media platform I've designed and built with React, JSX, JS, CSS modules
 and Firebase integration for Auth, Database and Storage. Authenticated users can set up their profile,
 post their thoughts, check out other users profile pages and posts, like them and scroll through the
 homepage feeds.
- An Expenses chart app (CRUD) I've built with React and styled with CSS and bootstrap. Where users
 can add items, filter by years, edit items and delete them. Including a chart diagram and a calculator.

2018 - Present - Active Artist and Musician under the name "Noamle"

I'm a singer, songwriter, music producer and a visual artist. As "Noamle" I've released 2 albums, 2 EPs, Singles and music videos.

Education

- 2023 Online courses for Advanced React, for TypeScript and for NodeJS.
- 2021 SheCodes USA Front-end, React and responsive web development Intensive studies of all major technologies, languages and softwares related to front-end and web development. During the studies we were faced with multiple exercises, assignments and real-time projects.
- 2018 2019 Music production and sound design studies at "Catalyst music" (formerly "dbs music").
- Graduated with honor 12 years of formal education and received high school diploma.

Languages

Hebrew - Native English - Fluent

Citizenships

Israeli EU Citizenship